<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
    android:background="#EEE"
    tools:context=".FreeStudyMaterial">

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_marginTop="5dp"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_marginStart="5dp"
        android:orientation="vertical"
        android:layout_marginEnd="5dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="50dp">

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/fsm_title_0"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="Title"
            android:textColor="#000"
            android:textAllCaps="true"
            android:textSize="20sp"
            android:textAlignment="center" />

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/fsm_details_0"
            android:layout_marginTop="5dp"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="By Aman Kaushik, 13/12/2020 08:40"
            android:textColor="#888"
            android:textStyle="italic"
            android:textSize="13sp"
            android:textAlignment="center" />

        <View
            android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="1dp"
            android:background="#000" />

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/fsm_content_0"
            android:layout_marginTop="5dp"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. This is a cat and this is a hat. "
            android:textColor="#444"
            android:padding="10dp"
            android:layout_marginStart="10dp"
            android:layout_marginEnd="10dp"
            android:textStyle="italic"
            android:textSize="16sp"/>

    </LinearLayout>

</ScrollView>